A Guide to the Register of Regulations records of the Virginia Code Commission, 1937-2021.
Library of Virginia
- Register of Regulations records, 1937-2021.
  - Accession 53993 (1970-2020, 5 cubic feet).
    - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1987-1999. (Box 2)
    - Rhabilitative Services, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 2008-2011. (Box 2)
    - Social Services, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1980-2008. (Box 2)
    - Social Services, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1994-2020. (Box 2)
    - Education Assistance Authority, 1973-2019. (Box 3)
    - Education Loan Authority - Correspondence, 1975-1994. (Box 3)
    - Education Loan Authority - Regulatory review, 1978-1993. (Box 3)
    - Funeral Directors and Embalmers, Board for - Correspondence, 1977-2018. (Box 3)
    - Governor's Employment and Training Dept. - Correspondence, 1998. (Box 3)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of - Actions/Issues, 1975-1997. (Box 3)
    - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1975-1997, 1980-1994. (Box 3)
    - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1994-2019. (Box 3)
    - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Correspondence, 1975-1992. (Box 3)
    - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Regulatory review, 1994-2017. (Box 3)
    - Human Resource Management, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1990-2004. (Box 3)
    - Human Resource Management, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1996-2019. (Box 3)
    - Health Services Cost Review Council - Correspondence, 1993-1994. (Box 3)
    - Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission - Correspondence, 2000. (Box 3)
    - Labor and Industry, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1978-2010. (Box 3)
    - Labor and Industry, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 2001-2019. (Box 3)
    - Long-Term Care Administrators, Board of - Regulatory review, 2008-2018. (Box 3)
    - Library of Virginia - Correspondence, 1984-2012. (Box 3)
    - Longwood University - Correspondence, 1994-2004. (Box 3)
    - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1984-2019. (Box 3)
    - Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1995-2008. (Box 3)
    - Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1995-2007. (Box 3)
    - Mines, Minerals, and Energy, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1992-2009, 2006-2009. (Box 3)
    - Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 2001-2019. (Box 3)
    - Marine Resources Commission - Correspondence, 1998-2005. (Box 3)
    - Marine Resources Commission - Regulatory review, 1989-1994. (Box 3)
    - Motor Vehicle Dealers Board - Correspondence, 1996-2019. (Box 3)
    - Nursing Home Administrators, Board for - Correspondence, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Norfolk State University - Correspondence, 1989. (Box 3)
    - Optometry, Board for - Regulatory review, 2001-2018. (Box 3)
    - OTR - Correspondence, 1973-1979. (Box 3)
    - Pharmacy, Board for - Regulatory review, 2005-2018. (Box 3)
    - Professional and Occupational Regulation, Board of - Correspondence, 1985-1999. (Box 3)
    - Professional and Occupational Regulation, Board of - Regulatory review, 1986-2019. (Box 3)
    - Audiology and Speech Language Pathology, Board of - Correspondence, 1973-2008. (Box 3)
    - Elections, State Board of - Regulatory review, 2013. (Box 3)
    - State Lottery Board - Correspondence, 1988-1991. (Box 3)
    - State Milk Commission - Correspondence, 1974-2003. (Box 3)
    - Natural Resources, Secretary of - Regulatory review, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth - Correspondence, 1984-1993. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Soil and Water Conservation Board - Correspondence, 1974-2019. (Box 4)
    - Taxation, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1973-2009. (Box 4)
    - Taxation, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1994-2019. (Box 4)
    - Treasury, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1973-1990. (Box 4)
    - Treasury, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1994-2018. (Box 4)
    - University of Virginia - Correspondenced, 1984. (Box 4)
    - Aviation, Dept. of - Correspondenced, 1973-1993. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Alcohol Safety Action Program - Correspondence, 1988-1990. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Commission for the Arts - Correspondence, 1974-1986. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University - Correspondence, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Aging, Dept. for the - Correspondence, 1983-1989. (Box 4)
    - Aging, Dept. for the - Regulatory review, 1994-2018. (Box 4)
    - Health, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1971-2011. (Box 4)
    - Health, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1983-2019. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Employment Commission - Correspondence, 1975-2016. (Box 4)
    - Veterinary Medicine, Board for - Correspondence, 1975-2010. (Box 4)
    - Veterinary Medicine, Board for - Regulatory review, 2000-2018. (Box 4)
    - Parole Board - Correspondence, 1978-2012. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Correspondence, 1997. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Racing Commission - Correspondence, 1990-2004. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Racing Commission - Regulatory review, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Retirement System - Correspondence, 1973-1991. (Box 4)
    - Virginia State Bar - Correspondence, 1993-1994. (Box 4)
    - Virginia State Police - Correspondence, 1973-1994. (Box 4)
    - Virginia State Police - Regulatory review, 1994-2014. (Box 4)
    - State Water Control Board - Correspondence, 1988-2011. (Box 4)
    - State Water Control Board - Governor's comments, 1988-1990. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Waste Management Board - Correspondence, 1988-2015. (Box 4)
    - Waste Management Facility Operators, Board for, 2012-2019. (Box 4)
    - Waste Management Board - Regulatory review, 1992-2020. (Box 4)
    - Professional Soil Scientists, Wetland Professionals and Geologists - Regulatory review, 2012-2019. (Box 4)
    - Industrial Building Authority - Regulatory review, 2011-2012. (Box 4)
    - Physical Therapy, Board of - Regulatory review, 2018. (Box 4)
    - Opticians, Board of - Regulatory review, 2011. (Box 4)
    - Hearing Aid Specialists and Opticians, Board for - Regulatory review, 2012-2019. (Box 4)
    - Geology, Board for - Regulatory review, 2011. (Box 4)
    - Fair Housing Board - Regulatory review, 20212-2019. (Box 4)
    - Health Professions, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 2012-2019. (Box 4)
    - Common Interest Community Board - Regulatory review, 2011-2019. (Box 4)
    - Accountancy, Board of - Regulatory review, 2017-2018. (Box 4)
    - Contractors, Board for - Regulatory review, 2011-2019. (Box 4)
    - Branch Pilots, Board for - Regulatory review, 2011-2019. (Box 4)
    - Barbers and Cosmetology, Board for, 2011-2019. (Box 4)
    - Auctioneers Board - Regulatory review, 20. (Box 4)
    - Asbestos, Lead, Mold and Home Inspectors - Regulatory review, 2011-2019. (Box 4)
    - Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers, and Landscape Architects, Board for - Regulatory review, 2011-2019. (Box 4)
    - Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage System Professionals, Board for - Regulatory review, 2012-2019. (Box 4)
    - Real Estate Appraiser Board - Regulatory review, 2012-2019. (Box 4)
    - Psychology, Board of - Regulatory review, 2012-2020. (Box 4)
    - Real Estate Board - Regulatory review, 2012-2019. (Box 4)
    - State Milk Commission - Regulatory review, 2003-2017. (Box 4)
    - State Milk Commission - Commission orders, 1774-2010. (Box 4)
    - Erratum: Health, Dept. of - Biosolids, 1995. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Social Services, Dept. of - Investigation of Child Abuse and Neglect in out of family complaints, 1994. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Nursing Home Administrators, Board for, 1990. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Virginia Energy Assistance Program, 1994. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Social Services, Dept. of, 1989-1994. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Determining domicile and eligibility for in-state tuition, 1995. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Virginia Scholars Program, 1993. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Virginia Health Services Cost Review Council, 1990. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Energy, Dept. of - Vertical ventilation holes, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Child Day-Care Council, 1993. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of - Criminal history record, 1990. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of - Dealer advertising practices, 1990. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Optometry, Board for, 1992. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Transportation, Dept. of - Jamestown-Scotland Ferry, 1994. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Relocation Assistance, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Veterinary Medicine, Board for, 1990. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Supervision fee rules, 1990. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Virginia Delinquency Prevention and Youth Development Act, 1990. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Pharmacy, Board for, 1988. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Taxation, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Lottery Board, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Air Pollution Control Board, 1990-1995. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Asbestos, Lead and Home Inspectors, Board for, 1989, 1994. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Water and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage System Professionals, 1990, 1992. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Real Estate Board, 1991-1992. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: State Water Control Board, 1992-1994, 1998. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 5)
    - Erratum: Funeral Directors and Embalmers, Board for, undated. (Box 5)